[

    {
        "question": "Pair this please 1",
        "answers": [ "book", "jumper", "pencil", "car", "hat", "cake", "socks" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "könyv", "pullóver", "ceruza", "autó", "sapka", "sütemény", "zokni" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45,
        "star": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Pair this please 2",
        "answers": [ "pen", "bag", "toothbrush", "T-Shirt", "hairbrush", "guitar", "baloon" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "toll", "táska", "fogkefe", "póló", "hajkefe", "gitár", "lufi" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45,
        "star": false

    },
    {
        "question": "Pair this please 3",
        "answers": [ "towel", "pencilcase", "dog", "train", "shoes", "cat", "Dad", "Mum" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "törölköző", "tolltartó", "kutya", "vonat", "cipők", "macska", "apa", "anya" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45,
        "star": false

    },
    {
        "question": "Pair Colors",
        "answers": [ "orange", "red", "blue", "pink", "yellow", "green", "black", "white" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "narancssárga", "piros", "kék", "rózsaszín", "sárga", "zöld", "fekete", "fehér" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45,
        "star": false

    },
    {
        "question": "Pair animals",
        "answers": [ "tiger", "monkey", "a zebra", "snake", "krokodil", "lion", "parrot", "cheetah" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "tigris", "majom", "egy zebra", "kígyó", "crocodile", "oroszlán", "papagáj", "gepárd" ],
        "answerLanguage": "quiet",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45,
        "star": false

    }
    ,
    {
        "question": "Pair this please 4",
        "answers": [ "chair", "table", "pen", "teacher", "book", "clock", "loud", "quiet" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "szék", "asztal", "toll", "tanár", "könyv", "óra", "hangos", "csendes" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45,
        "star": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Pair this loud",
        "answers": [ "loud", "slow", "I'm hungry", "fish", "coffee", "lemonade", "water", "point" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "hangos", "lassú", "éhes vagyok", "hal", "kávé", "limonádé", "víz", "mutat" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45,
        "star": false

    },
    {
        "question": "Pair this sentences",
        "answers": [ "Listen and say", "Do you like?", "Be careful!", "My turn", "Go back to start", "'I don't like'", "I like", "Thank You" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "Halgasd és mond", "Szereted?", "Légy óvatos", "Én jövök / én jövök sorra", "Menj vissza az elejére", "Nem szeretem", "Szerem", "Köszönöm" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45,
        "star": false

    },
    {
        "question": "Pair this x1",
        "answers": [ "finish", "wheat", "cereal", "cakes", "brother", "look", "sister", "bug" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "befejez", "búza", "gabona", "sütemények", "fiútestvér", "néz", "lánytestvár", "bogár" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45,
        "star": false

    },
    {
        "question": "Pair this x2",
        "answers": [ "spider", "crab", "star", "circle", "triangle", "ears", "firefighter", "climb", "walk" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "pók", "rák", "csillag", "kör", "áromszög", "fülek", "tűzoltó", "mászik", "sétál" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45,
        "star": false

    },
        {
        "question": "Pair this x3",
        "answers": [ "paint", "spell", "count", "sing", "write", "swim", "jump", "draw" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "fest", "betűz", "számol", "énekel", "ír", "úszik", "ugrik", "rajzol" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45,
        "star": false

    },
        {
        "question": "Pair this x4",
        "answers": [ "morning", "afternoon", "evening", "night", "noon", "happy", "sad" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "reggel", "délután", "este", "éjszaka", "dél", "boldog", "szomorú" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45,
        "star": false

    },
        {
        "question": "Pair this x5",
        "answers": [ "tall", "short", "big", "small", "students", "doctor", "pilot", "actor" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "magas", "alacsony", "nagy", "kicsi", "tanuló", "doktor", "pilóta", "színész" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45,
        "star": false

    },
        {
        "question": "Pair this x6",
        "answers": [ "police officer", "fly", "walk", "climb", "can", "can't", "read", "footballer" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "rendőr", "repül", "sétál", "mászik", "tud", "nem tud", "olvas", "focista" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45,
        "star": false

    },
        {
        "question": "Pair this x8",
        "answers": [ "artist", "eyes", "nose", "hand", "mouth", "write", "sing", "can't" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "művész", "szem", "orr", "kéz", "száj", "ír", "énekel", "nem tudja" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45,
        "star": false

    },
    {
        "question": "Pair this please 5",
        "answers": [ "listen", "fish", "cheese", "yoghurt", "bread", "rice", "see" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "hallgat", "hal", "sajt", "joghurt", "kenyér", "rizs", "lát" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45,
        "star": false

    },
    {
        "question": "Pair this please 6",
        "answers": [ "rice", "pasta", "fields", "cow", "milk", "run", "climb trees" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "rizs", "tészta", "mezők", "tehén", "tej", "fut", "fára mászik" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45,
        "star": false

    },
    {
        "question": "Pair this please 7",
        "answers": [ "ice cream", "Goodbye !", "look", "cow", "milk", "fly", "sunhat", "pasta" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "jégkrém", "Viszont látásra !", "nézd", "tehén", "tej", "repül", "kalap", "tészta" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 60,
        "star": false

    },
    {
        "question": "Pair this please 8",
        "answers": [ "I like",  "Do You like?", "taste", "touch", "smell", "hear", "kezek" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "Szeretem",  "Szereted?", "ízlel", "érint", "szagol", "hall", "hands" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45,
        "star": false

    },
    {
        "question": "Pair this please 9",
        "answers": [ "I hear",  "I don't hear", "with my eyes", "with my nose", "I see", "I don't like", "kezek" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "Hallom",  "Nem hallom", "szememmel", "orrommal", "látom", "nem szeretem", "hands" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45,
        "star": false

    },
    {
        "question": "Pair this please 10",
        "answers": [ "butter",  "I see", "mouth", "see", "soup", "and", "thank you", "face" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "vaj",  "látom", "száj", "lát", "leves", "és", "közönöm", "arc" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 45,
        "star": false

    },
    {
        "question": "Pair this please 11",
        "answers": [ "kitchen", "bedroom", "bathroom", "sitting room", "hall", "garden", "trainers", "dress" ],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "konyha", "hálószoba", "fürdőszoba", "nappali", "előszoba", "kert", "tornacipő", "ruha" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 60,
        "star": false

    }
    ,
    {
        "question": "Pair this please 12",
        "answers": [ "left", "right", "bathroom", "sitting room", "shorts", "sandals", "trainers"],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "bal", "jobb", "fürdőszoba", "nappali", "rövidnadrág", "szandálok", "tornacipő" ],
        "answerLanguage": "en-GB",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 60,
        "star": false

    }

]